[{"answer": "We know that the U.S. has been on a heightened state of alert, Piers, for some time now, specifically -- specifically because on Sunday is the 10th anniversary of 9/11.", "docId": "110908pmt", "aSentId": 12, "question": "What do we know, do you think?", "qSentId": 11}, {"answer": "I do know that that is taking place, obviously, in New York, not here, not involving the White House.", "docId": "110908pmt", "aSentId": 36, "question": "What can you tell me about this?", "qSentId": 35}, {"answer": "I haven't seen anything exactly like this.", "docId": "110908pmt", "aSentId": 95, "question": "But have you seen anything quite like this in terms of the warning they have given, the strength of the warning, the number of official bodies coming out now making statements, briefings and so on?", "qSentId": 94}, {"answer": "Well, we certainly need to deal with the sinking economy, the growth that we're seeing now is 1 percent or less, far below what was projected just a few months ago.", "docId": "110908pmt", "aSentId": 131, "question": "What is your reaction and do you think he'll get this through?", "qSentId": 130}, {"answer": "Well, I know that the president was briefed first thing this morning.", "docId": "110908pmt", "aSentId": 145, "question": "What do you know about this?", "qSentId": 144}, {"answer": "The president takes all threats to our country very seriously, and that's why he's asked his team to redouble our efforts.", "docId": "110908pmt", "aSentId": 155, "question": "What makes you taking this one so seriously?", "qSentId": 154}, {"answer": "Well, I think that he's received a lot of very positive reaction to the speech.", "docId": "110908pmt", "aSentId": 161, "question": "What do you think his reaction is now that he's made it to the early reaction you've been receiving to the speech?", "qSentId": 160}, {"answer": "Look, this isn't a matter of the president in or out of office.", "docId": "110908pmt", "aSentId": 174, "question": "If it doesn't work, if we get to next summer and unemployment has continued to rise, would you as the administration accept that the American public would have a right to vote the president out of office?", "qSentId": 173}, {"answer": "Well, no, we're encouraged.", "docId": "110908pmt", "aSentId": 188, "question": "Are you encouraged by their reaction or do you think you may be facing a pretty uphill battle here?", "qSentId": 187}, {"answer": "Well, I think it's significant, Piers.", "docId": "110908pmt", "aSentId": 216, "question": "Is it going to work?", "qSentId": 215}, {"answer": "I think it will make a big difference.", "docId": "110908pmt", "aSentId": 227, "question": "I mean, is this going to actually make a big enough difference?", "qSentId": 226}, {"answer": "It feels to me like this is more kind of spurring demand in the short term.", "docId": "110908pmt", "aSentId": 234, "question": "And if so, in what kind of time scale?", "qSentId": 233}, {"answer": "Well, I think that's what we need to do.", "docId": "110908pmt", "aSentId": 243, "question": "What did you make of his ambitious plans of America to stop being the world's biggest consumer and perhaps go back to what they used to be really good at, which is become one of the world's great producers and manufacturers again?", "qSentId": 242}, {"answer": "No, not too much.", "docId": "110908pmt", "aSentId": 255, "question": "Ron Paul, what do you make of it, not very impressed then?", "qSentId": 254}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I think you state the problem that we have.", "docId": "110908pmt", "aSentId": 275, "question": "The country may not have much money, but he's got to do something, doesn't he?", "qSentId": 274}, {"answer": "Well, I think it was -- the president was trying to give a jolt to the economy.", "docId": "110908pmt", "aSentId": 299, "question": "Mr. Brinkley, your reaction to the jobs speech tonight, please?", "qSentId": 298}, {"answer": "Well, I don't think a trillion dollars would have been credible.", "docId": "110908pmt", "aSentId": 313, "question": "Should he have really gone for it, put a trillion dollars behind this?", "qSentId": 312}, {"answer": "Well, the phraseology you talk about is specific, credible and unconfirmed.", "docId": "110908pmt", "aSentId": 352, "question": "How credible does it sound to you?", "qSentId": 351}, {"answer": "What I've heard of the threat -- I actually heard it was New York or Washington.", "docId": "110908pmt", "aSentId": 366, "question": "What are you expecting from this press conference that we're going to get to in a moment?", "qSentId": 365}, {"answer": "Thank you, Mr. Mayor.", "docId": "110908pmt", "aSentId": 413, "question": "Jane?", "qSentId": 412}, {"answer": "Thank you, Mr. Mayor.", "docId": "110908pmt", "aSentId": 426, "question": "Ray?", "qSentId": 425}, {"answer": "Commissioner, thank you.", "docId": "110908pmt", "aSentId": 447, "question": "Mr. Mayor?", "qSentId": 446}, {"answer": "That's Michael Bloomberg there in a press conference about the terror threat tonight, which is believed to be involving the tenth anniversary of 9/11.", "docId": "110908pmt", "aSentId": 453, "question": "Can you tell us what forced your hand to make this now?", "qSentId": 452}, {"answer": "I think that they are using measured language, which is meant to inspire people to pay attention and to report what they see because of a heightened threat picture, but also very measured language not to cause overdue concern or panic.", "docId": "110908pmt", "aSentId": 457, "question": "What was your view when you heard the comments they made?", "qSentId": 456}, {"answer": "The latest information, Piers, is that three people might possibly be involved.", "docId": "110908pmt", "aSentId": 479, "question": "Susan, what is the latest information you have?", "qSentId": 478}, {"answer": "Absolutely not.", "docId": "110908pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "Are you happy about that?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "Absolutely, I would agree with that.", "docId": "110908pmt", "aSentId": 506, "question": "Dave Ramsey, would you agree with that?", "qSentId": 505}, {"answer": "Well, I don't, because what comes with this is the ticket that we go further into debt.", "docId": "110908pmt", "aSentId": 522, "question": "Do you actually believe that what the president outlined today is going to stimulate the jobs market enough to make any substantial difference?", "qSentId": 521}, {"answer": "Certainly these are two areas that already on edge with the anniversary of 9/11, the tenth anniversary rolling around.", "docId": "110908pmt", "aSentId": 533, "question": "Back to CNN's Susan Candiotti now with the latest breaking news on the terror threat against New York and D.C. Susan, what have you got?", "qSentId": 532}]